<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BoardGamerWeekly blog on BGW blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.boardgamerweekly.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BoardGamerWeekly blog on BGW blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>BoardGamerWeekly</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.boardgamerweekly.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Everdell Review</title>
      <link>https://blog.boardgamerweekly.com/reviews/everdell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.boardgamerweekly.com/reviews/everdell/</guid>
      <description>Everdell is also one of the games I backed on Kickstarter. The campaign was running in January 2018. and collected almost half a million dollars. It promised a great looking game that is easy to learn and fun to play. The promise is fulfilled! Several expansions for Everdell were also kickstarted in the meantime, but this review is for the base game only, and the solo variant of it.
About the game In Everdell, you are competing with other players to build your own critters city which is more valuable than cities of other players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D-Day Dice Pocket Review</title>
      <link>https://blog.boardgamerweekly.com/reviews/d-day-dice-pocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 01:01:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.boardgamerweekly.com/reviews/d-day-dice-pocket/</guid>
      <description>D-Day Dice Pocket is one of the games I backed on Kickstarter. The Kickstarter campaign was actually for D-Day Dice: 2nd Edition and D-Day Dice Pocket came in the package on higher pledge levels. I&amp;rsquo;m yet to try the main D-Day Dice game, but judging from the experience while playing its smaller brother, it might actually be quite fun.
D-Day Dice Pocket actually contains two games in one small package - D-Day Dice Battle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://blog.boardgamerweekly.com/2020/04/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 01:01:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.boardgamerweekly.com/2020/04/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to my attempt of blogging about board gaming hobby. My name is Miroslav Popovic and I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer by trade. Hopefully, this blog will be more productive than the other one about the software development.
My first foray into the world of modern board gaming happened several years ago, when I discovered board games category on Kickstarter. I quickly became addicted. Now I&amp;rsquo;m a (not so) proud owner of 150+ board games.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>